inboundwriter.com 2014-05-13

# Privacy Policy • InboundWriter

This Privacy Policy describes the privacy practices of Eightfold Logic, a Delaware corporation (“Eightfold Logic”). It is intended to inform our customers and visitors to our and our customers’ websites, about Eightfold Logic’s data collection and usage relating to information we may collect on our website as well as information we process through Eightfold Logic’s products and services (collectively “Eightfold Logic Products”).

Eightfold Logic Privacy Policy – Effective May 19, 2009

By submitting your information to us or by installing and/or using the Eightfold Logic Products, you are consenting to our use of your data as described in this Privacy Policy.

As our business changes, our Privacy Policy will also change, and we reserve the right to change how we handle the information we collect. You should check our website frequently to see any changes to our Privacy Policy. If a material change has been made to our Privacy Policy, we may also notify our registered users via e-mail.

### Information Collection and Use – Our Website

We collect contact information, such as name, address, email address and/or phone number, and credit card information for online registration of Eightfold Logic Products. We use this information to provide services that are requested by our website visitors, customers or prospective customers (for example, to respond to your request for further information about us or our services, send a requested newsletter or white paper, or provision a customer to use Eightfold Logic Products).

We consider your personal information highly confidential and will not pass it on to anyone outside of Eightfold Logic and its affiliates and resellers, except where required to do so by law or to prevent a crime or violation of our customer contract. Affiliates, and resellers are authorized agents/resellers of Eightfold Logic Products. We may pass on your information to them to complete a particular service or offer you requested from our website.

If you participate in any customer case studies or online discussions posted on the Eightfold Logic website, you should be aware that any information you share is visible to other users. Personally identifiable information you submit to one of these forums can be read, collected, or used by other individuals to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

We may collect general demographic and profile data on our website from time to time in order to better understand and assist our customers and to help improve our site. This data is used only in anonymous form and does not identify you or your personal details. We also reserve the right to aggregate personally identifiable information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to third parties for marketing, promotional, and other purposes as long as we do not disclose any information that could be used to identify you personally.

Third-Party Service Providers. We use other third parties to provide certain services, such as sending postal mail and e-mail, or processing credit card payments, on our behalf. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.

Service-related Announcements. If you are a customer of Eightfold Logic, we will send you strictly service-related announcements when it is necessary to do so. For instance, we may send you an email if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. You may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

Customer Service. Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we may send you a Welcome email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you, by email or telephone, in response to your inquiries.

### Information We Process Through Eightfold Logic Products

What Information Does Eightfold Logic Collect From its Customers and How Is That Data Used? Our customers are businesses, not individuals. To the extent that any personal contact information is collected through Eightfold Logic Products, we use this contact information for business purposes, such as responding to requests for information about Eightfold Logic Products and services, providing access to certain services, and for registration of Eightfold Logic Products.

### IP Addresses and Cookies

When you connect to our website, our web servers recognize your IP address and certain other information about your computer. This is necessary to deliver downloaded products, administer the web server, and track problems. We also uses what are called “cookies” to store and retrieve customer information through a user’s web browser. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and normally can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies permit a website to serve you more effectively. Our customers may also use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable information for internal evaluation of their website.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies.

### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate your account by submitting a request via Support page or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. Eightfold Logic will respond to all access requests within 30 days.

### Security

Eightfold Logic Products have security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use industry standard SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) encryption to protect your privacy and account details.

### Other Sites

Our website contains links to other sites. We have no control over and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any of these websites or any other websites.

### Right to Opt Out

You have the following options for removing your information from our database to not receive future communications or services:

  * You can send us an email requesting removal to optout@eightfoldlogic.com.
  * You can send us regular mail requesting removal to the following postal address: Webmaster, Eightfold Logic, 1900 S. Norfolk Street, Suite 219, San Mateo, CA 94403.
  * If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter, customer service and/or promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at optout@eightfoldlogic.com.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose or release information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms Of Service And Conditions Of Use and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Eightfold Logic, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

### Contacting the Web Site Administrator

We welcome comments and questions about the Eightfold Logic site or any other aspect of our web site or products or services, including this Privacy Policy. Please contact us by emailing us at optout@eightfoldlogic.com; or by sending regular mail to Webmaster, Eightfold Logic, 1900 S. Norfolk Street, Suite 219, San Mateo, CA 94403 U.S.A. Please remember to include your postal address, email address and phone number with your correspondence.
